<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<!-- QUOTES >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_BORROS_BARATHEON_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Go home, pup, and tell the bitch, your mother, that the Lord of Storm's End is not a dog she can whistle up. </Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_DALTON_GREYJOY_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text> “In his 15th year, he avenged his uncle's death in battle, but he took a dozen wounds and emerged from the fight drenched head to heel in blood. From that day forth, men called him 'the Red Kraken'. ”[NEWLINE]– Euron Greyjoy about Dalton</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_AEGONII_TARGARYEN_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Let the ravens fly that the realm may know the pretender is dead, and their true king is coming home to reclaim his father’s throne.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_LYONEL_TYRELL_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text> “Daeron the First succeeded at great cost and reigned in Dorne for a few glorious months. One night, his steward (Lyonel) pulled down the sash by his bed to summon his consorts. Instead, the canopy split open and a hundred red scorpions fell on him.”[NEWLINE]– Oberyn Martell about Lyonel</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- LEADERS >>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_CREGAN_STARK_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"  Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cregan Stark was a Lord of Winterfell, Warden of the North, and head of House Stark. He briefly served as Hand of the King for Aegon III Targaryen after the Dance of the Dragons. Cregan pledged his support to the blacks during the Dance of the Dragons. Lord Roderick Dustin commanded the first host of northmen who marched south, known as the Winter Wolves, men who feared a long winter. They were followed by a larger host led by Lord Cregan, many of whose men were childless, homeless, unwed, or young sons marching to war to spare their families from supporting them in winter. Cregan's host was denied combat, however, by the poisoning of King Aegon II Targaryen. Lord Stark had intended to punish the leaders of Aegon II's greens, but Lord Corlys Velaryon had already sent envoys seeking peace. Cregan held court at King's Landing for six days, a time known as the Hour of the Wolf. Acting in the name of the eleven-year-old King Aegon III Targaryen, who named him Hand of the King, Cregan had twenty-two men arrested for the murder of Aegon II, among them Lord Larys Strong and Corlys Velaryon.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_ELMO_TULLY_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"  Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ser Elmo Tully was a knight of House Tully, whom became Lord of Riverrun and head of House Tully after the death of his grandfather Lord Grover Tully. Lord Grover Tully wanted to support King Aegon II Targaryen and the greens during the Dance of the Dragons, but he was too aged and his grandson, Ser Elmo, kept the Tully banners at Riverrun. Elmo died while marching with the blacks forty-nine days later, however. He was succeeded by his son, Ser Kermit Tully.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_JEYNE_ARRYN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"  Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jeyne Arryn, also called the Maiden of the Vale, was Lady of the Eyrie and head of House Arryn. She ruled the Vale of Arryn during the Targaryen civil war known as the Dance of the Dragons. At the start of the civil war called the Dance of the Dragons, Prince Jacaerys Velaryon flew north on his dragon Vermax, to foster allies for the cause of his mother, Rhaenyra Targaryen, herself the daughter of Aemma Arryn. One of the places he went to was the Eyrie. There, he treated with Lady Jeyne and made a promise to her. Jeyne brought the Eyrie to the side of the blacks during the civil war. Though snows closed the passes through the Mountains of the Moon, Jeyne sent men by sea by way of Gulltown to join the queen's hosts.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_BORROS_BARATHEON_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"  Language="en_US">
			<Text>Borros Baratheon was Lord of Storm's End and head of House Baratheon during the Dance of the Dragons. At the start of the Dance of the Dragons both the blacks and the greens hoped to win Lord Borros over to their cause. Prince Aemond Targaryen hoped to wed one of his four eligible daughters to win House Baratheon over to the greens, and arrived on dragonback to do so. Prince Lucerys Velaryon arrived soon after to win Borros to the black cause. Eyewitness accounts varied, with some saying Lord Baratheon was embarrassed for Lucerys to find him treating with Aemond (as Borros's father had been a supporter of Princess Rhaenys Targaryen), while others say he relished the prospect of both factions competing for his aid. Borros kept the armies of the stormlands out of heavy fighting for most of the war, but he eventually took King's Landing during the Moon of the Three Kings. Borros's army was defeated by the Lads and their rivermen in the battle of the Kingsroad. Borros is said to have killed twelve knights, along with Lords Darry and Mallister, before falling against Lord Kermit Tully.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_JASON_LANNISTER_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"  Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jason Lannister was Lord of Casterly Rock and head of House Lannister during the reigns of Viserys I and Aegon II Targaryen. During the civil war known as the Dance of the Dragons (129 AC-131 AC) Jason was loyal to King Aegon II and the greens against Rhaenyra's claim, while Tyland was Aegon's master of coin. Jason was killed by Pate of Longleaf in the Battle at the Red Fork, however, which left Casterly Rock in considerable disarray. Jason's widow, Lady Johanna Lannister, defended the westerlands from the Red Kraken, Lord Dalton Greyjoy.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_DALTON_GREYJOY_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"  Language="en_US">
			<Text>Dalton Greyjoy, known as the Red Kraken, was Lord of the Iron Islands, Lord Reaper of Pyke, and head of House Greyjoy during the final days of Viserys I Targaryen and then the Dance of the Dragons. He is regarded as a great hero of the ironborn of the Iron Islands. The greens of Aegon II Targaryen offered Dalton the position of master of ships and the admiralty to replace Ser Tyland Lannister, who had been made master of coin, if Dalton would bring his ships around Westeros to battle Lord Corlys Velaryon, the Sea Snake. Instead of leaping to the offer, Dalton waited to see what the blacks had to offer. On the black council, Prince Daemon Targaryen suggested appealing to Dalton's bloodlust to bring him on the side of Rhaenyra Targaryen. The Red Kraken chose black over green, deciding to attack the nearby westerlands, vulnerable with Lord Jason Lannister campaigning in the riverlands.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_ALIANDRA_MARTELL_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"  Language="en_US">
			<Text>Aliandra Martell was a ruling Princess of Dorne and head of House Nymeros Martell. She saw herself as a new Nymeria. She was a fiery young woman who encouraged her lords and knights to prove themselves to her by raiding in the Dornish Marches. Aliandra showed great favor to Lord Alyn Velaryon, when he visited Sunspear. They met during his first great journey, when his campaign to defend the westerlands from Dalton Greyjoy.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_RHAENYRA_TARGARYEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"  Language="en_US">
			<Text>Princess Rhaenyra Targaryen, cheered as the Realm's Delight when she was young and later called the Half-Year Queen, was the first-born child of King Viserys I Targaryen. Rhaenyra was King Viserys I's only living child by his first wife, Aemma of House Arryn. At the age of eight she was made her father's heir and grew up expecting to become the first ruling Queen of Westeros. Her claim to the Iron Throne was challenged by her younger half-brother, Aegon II Targaryen, sparking the civil war known as the Dance of the Dragons. Rhaenyra's personal sigil was the normal Targaryen heraldry (a three-headed red dragon on a black field), quartered with the moon-and-falcon sigil of House Arryn (for her mother Aemma Arryn), and the silver seahorse on sea green of House Velaryon (for her first husband Laenor Velaryon, as well as for the Velaryons in general, who were among her major supporters). During the Dance, her faction used her personal heraldry as their battle-flag.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_AEGONII_TARGARYEN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"  Language="en_US">
			<Text>Aegon II Targaryen was the sixth Targaryen king to sit the Iron Throne, succeeding his father, Viserys I Targaryen, as Lord of the Seven Kingdoms. His ascent was disputed by his older half-sister, Princess Rhaenyra Targaryen, who had been their father's designated heir. Aegon and Rhaenyra fought for the throne in the civil war the singers called the Dance of the Dragons, in which both siblings perished. His dragon was Sunfyre the Golden and for his personal sigil he took a golden dragon instead of a red Targaryen one, indicating his mount. During the Dance of the Dragons, his faction used his personal heraldry as their battle-flag.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_LYONEL_TYRELL_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1"  Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lyonel Tyrell was the Lord of Highgarden and head of House Tyrell during the Dance of the Dragons and the conquest of Dorne. But Lord Lyonel was an infant during the Dance of the Dragons (129-131 AC), thus his mother ruled the Reach as his regent. Lord Lyonel fought beneath the Targaryen banner when the Young Dragon, King Daeron I Targaryen, sought to conquer Dorne. Upon his ascension in 157 AC, Daeron marched south with his armies and defeated the Dornishmen, becoming the first Targaryen king to conquer Dorne and unite all Seven Kingdoms for the first time. Lyonel faithfully, if perhaps too boldly, commanded the army that invaded Dorne via the Prince's Pass. After the Young Dragon's initial victory, Daeron appointed Lyonel as governor of Dorne. The Dornishmen, however, proved cunning and impossible to rule. Lyonel moved with his train from one keep to the next, chasing rebels out and keeping the knees of the Dornishmen bent. It was his custom to turn the lords of the keeps he stayed in out of their chambers and sleep in their place. One night at Sandstone, finding himself in a bed with a heavy velvet canopy, he pulled a sash near the pillows to summon a wench. When he did so, the canopy opened and a hundred red scorpions fell upon him. His death sparked new revolts, and in a fortnight all the work of the Young Dragon was undone, eventually bringing the about the death of King Daeron himself.</Text>
		</Row>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
